This is a real sixty-second Cockroach Crawler demo: install the
package, run a deterministic crawl, verify the denial, and inspect
the source record.
Install one package. It exposes the command line, JavaScript library,
and strict agent adapter with no hosted account or signup.
The captured command authorizes the offline fixture and fixes page,
depth, request, per-page byte, total-byte, and delay ceilings before execution.
The real result contains two structured pages, status, depth, and
content hashes. Removing the required network authority blocks dispatch and
returns zero pages.
The source adapter converts that crawl into a normalized evidence
record with source identity, adapter version, provenance, metadata, warnings, and
a separate record hash.
Use it for documentation retrieval, content quality checks, and bounded
agent research. Install locally, then review every limit at cockroachcrawler
dot com.