This proof starts a deterministic server on loopback. It uses
no internet connection, API key, account, or external side effect.
The real command explicitly authorizes loopback and fixes page, depth,
request, per-page byte, total-byte, and delay budgets.
The command returns two structured pages with status, depth, and
SHA-256 content hashes. The same seed without private-network authority is
denied.
Source doctor comes from the same credential-free runtime: web and
public GitHub ready, YouTube partial, and X and Reddit requiring
credentials.
The web adapter converts crawler output into normalized records with
source, type, adapter version, provenance, metadata, and a separate record
hash.